Free delivery **from 23,53 €**

Language and currency:

**en | €**

Country of collecting the order:

**Poland \[PL\]**

* Language
    
    de
    
    en
    
    fr
    
* Prices in
    
    €£ (1 € = 0.8673£) zł (1 € = 4.25zł) $ (1 € = 1.1333$)
    
    Country of collecting the order
    
    AlbaniaAlgeriaAustraliaAustria \[AT\]Belgium \[BE\]Bosnia and Herzegovina \[BIH\]Bulgaria \[BG\]CanadaChina Croatia \[HR\]Cyprus \[CY\]Czech Republic \[CZ\]Denmark \[DK\]EgyptEstonia \[EE\]Finland \[FI\]France \[FR\]Germany \[DE\]Greece \[GR\]Hungary \[HU\]Ierland \[IE\]IndiaIsle of ManItaly \[IT\]Latvia \[LV\]Liechtenstein \[LI\]Lithuania \[LT\]Luxembourg \[LU\]Malta \[MT\]Moldova \[MD\]Netherlands \[NL\]New ZealandNorthern Ireland \[NI\]Norway \[NO\]PeruPoland \[PL\]Portugal \[PT\]QatarRomania \[RO\]San MarinoSaudi ArabiaSerbia \[RS\]Slovakia \[SK\]Slovenia \[SI\]Spain \[ES\]Sweden \[SE\]Switzerland \[CH\]TurkeyUAEUkraine \[UA\]United Kingdom \[GB\]United States
    
* Apply changes

* 0

ProductQuantityPrice

Delivery cost from

        * \+ Show all
        * \+ Show all

Back

1. You are here:
2. [Home page](https://sps24.eu/)
3. Privacy Policy

##### Trusted Shops guarantee up to €20,000. You receive the purchased item or a refund.

Shopping lists

* 0
* Shopping lists

**How does a shopping list work?**

* Once logged in, you can place and store any number of products on your shopping list indefinitely.
* Adding a product to your shopping list does not automatically mean you have reserved it.
* For non-logged-in customers the shopping list is stored until the session expires (about 24h).

Privacy Policy
==============

 Data Controller and Definitions

Data Controller and Definitions
===============================

The data controller of Customers/Users of the Online Shop, also known as the Seller, is EPRIME MAREK MUCHA, tel. 537716596, NIP PL7481539761, REGON 160406809.

The data controller can be contacted at:

Address for letters: Szklary Górne 39, 59-335 Lubin;

The e-mail address: info@sps24.eu.

**User** - a natural person entering the website/websites of the Online Shop or using the services or functionalities described in this Policy.

**Customer** - a natural person having full legal capacity, a natural person who is a Consumer, a legal person or an organizational unit without legal personality, to which the Act grants legal capacity, which concludes a Distance Selling Agreement with the Seller.

**Online Shop** - an Internet service run by the Seller, available at electronic addresses (websites): https://sps24.eu through which the Customer/User may obtain information about the Goods and its availability and buy the Goods or order the service.

**Newsletter** - information, including commercial information within the meaning of the Act of 18 July 2002 on the provision of electronic services (Dz. U. z 2020 r. poz. 344) from the Seller, sent to the Customer/User by electronic means; its receipt is voluntary and requires the consent of the Customer/User.

**Account** - a set of data stored in the Online Shop and in the Seller's IT system concerning the Customer/User and orders placed by the Customer/User and the agreements concluded by the Customer/User, which enables the Customer/User to place orders and conclude agreements.

**GDPR** - Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC.

The Purposes, Legal Basis, and Period of Processing
---------------------------------------------------

In order to perform the Distance Selling Agreement, the Seller processes:

* Information concerning the User's device to ensure the correct functioning of the services: IP address of the computer, information contained in cookies or other similar technologies, session data, web browser data, device data, data concerning activity on the website, including on individual subpages.
* Geolocation data, if the User has consented to the service provider's access to geolocation. The geolocation data is used to provide more tailored offers of Goods and services.
* Users' personal data: name, surname, registered office address, correspondence address, e-mail address, telephone number, Tax Identification Number (NIP), bank account number, or other personal data required by the Administrator in the purchasing process.

This information does not contain identity data of the Users, but in combination with other information may constitute personal information. Therefore, the data controller extends full GDPR protection to them.

These data are processed in accordance with Article 6 section 1 letter b of the GDPR, for the purpose of providing a service, i.e., an agreement for the provision of services by electronic means in accordance with the Regulation, in accordance with Article 6 section 1 letter a of the GDPR, in accordance with consenting to the use of certain cookies or other similar technologies, as expressed by the appropriate settings of the Internet browser, in accordance with the Telecommunications Law or in accordance with consenting to geolocation. The data are processed until the end of the User's use of the Online Shop.

The Administrator undertakes to take all measures required under Article 32 of the RODO, i.e., taking into account the state of the art, the cost of implementation and the nature, scope, and purposes of the processing and the risk of violation of the rights or freedoms of natural persons of varying probability and seriousness, the Administrator implements appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure a level of security appropriate to that risk.

Marketing Activities of the Data Controller
-------------------------------------------

The data controller may place marketing information about his/her Goods or services on the Online Shop’s website. Such content shall be displayed by the data controller in accordance with Article 6 section 1 letter f of the GDPR, in accordance with the legitimate interest pursued by the data controller, in publishing the content related to the services provided and the promotional content of the actions in which the data controller is involved. At the same time, the action does not infringe the rights and freedoms of the Customers/Users, the Customers/Users expect to receive similar content, or even expect it or it is their direct purpose to visit the website(s) of the Online Shop.

* How to Buy

* Information

In the store we present the gross prices (incl. VAT).

* SPS24, Szklary Górne 39, 59-335 Lubin
